[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":25416,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":31865,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":2500,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":34367,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":6492,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":40861,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1635,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":42498,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3223,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":45721,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1119,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":46840,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one t o it. If  the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3503,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":50345,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1081,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":51427,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3504,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":54931,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":824,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":55756,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3504,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":59261,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3  because  3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1177,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":60439,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3087,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":63527,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":793,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":64322,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember , to per form +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2858,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":67181,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":774,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":67956,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free ","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3160,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":71116,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1066,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":72184,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2685,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":74870,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":906,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":75778,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3058,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":78836,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":695,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":79533,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":7484,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":87019,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, beca use 3 +< sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":15194,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":102215,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4823,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":107040,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":917,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":107957,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse  of an el ement is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2776,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":110734,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1111,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":111847,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2802,"trial_type":"q uestion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":114649,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":868,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":115519,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2753,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":118273,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":625,"trial_type":" feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":118899,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":2701,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":121601,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2600,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":124202,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the  left-mos t pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":4337,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":128540,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1 , 3, or  5 using just 2.","rt":18524,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":147065,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":3763,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":150830,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1392,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":152224,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an elem ent whic h can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":2363,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":154587,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":26241,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":180829,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a genera tor is a n element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":10576,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":191407,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":2172,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":193581,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":7813,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":201396,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1518,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":202916,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new opera tion. Af ter that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":12896,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":215813,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4110,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":219925,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":9760,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":229687,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":3504,"trial_type":"questio n","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":233193,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5087,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":238281,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":8130,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":246413,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":2916,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":249331,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4302,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":253635,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":5496,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":259132,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in  words h ow you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"5 is less than 9 so the standard answer of 4+1 is fine.","explanation_history":["5 is less than 9 so the standard answer of 5","5 is less than 9 so the standard answer of 4+1 is fine."],"response_history":["5"],"rt":30439,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":289574,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"Because 8+4 is larger than 9, we must subtract 9 from the answer, giving 12-9 which is 3.","explanation_history":["Because 8+4 is larger than 9, we must subtract 9 from the answer, giving 12-9 which is 3."],"response_history":["3"],"rt":34593,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":324170,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"The mathematical identity is 0 because 0 added to any number under +9 results in that number.","explanation_history":["The mathematical identity is 0 because 0 added to any number under +9 is it","The mathematical identity is 0 because 0 added to any number under +9 is i","The mathematical identity is 0 because 0 added to any number under +9 is ","The mathematical identity is 0 because 0 added to any number under +9 is","The mathematical identity is 0 because 0 added to any number under +9 i","The mathematical identity is 0 because 0 added to any number under +9 results in that number."],"response_history":["0"],"rt":69107,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":393280,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":[" 5","4"],"rt":7204,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":400487,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":2440,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":402929,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3208,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":406138,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"The inverse is 6 because 3+6 = 9.","explanation_history":["Tge u","Tge ","Tge","Tg","The inverse is 6 because 3 + 6","The inverse is 6 because 3 + ","The inverse is 6 because 3 +","The inverse is 6 because 3 ","The inverse is 6 because 3+6 = ","The inverse is 6 because 3+6 =","The inverse is 6 because 3+6  =","The inverse is 6 because 3+6  ","The inverse is 6 because 3+6 = 9, ","The inverse is 6 because 3+6 = 9,","The inverse is 6 because 3+6 = 9."],"response_history":["6"],"rt":24465,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":430604,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words  how you  got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"No. It can generate some numbers, but not all of them.","explanation_history":["No. It can","No. It ca","No. It c","No. It can generate some numbers, but not all of them."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":73045,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":503652,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"For every number 1 through 8, there is a combination of 3 under +9 that will allow us to reach it.","explanation_history":["For every number 1 through 9, there is a ","For every number 1 through ","For every number 1 through 8, there is a combination of 3+0","For every number 1 through  8, there  is a combination of 3+","For every number 1 through 8, there is a combination of 3 under +9 that will allow us to reach it."],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":45940,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":549595,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"Like the previous answer, we can reach every other number through some combination of 5 under +9.","explanation_history":["Like the previous answer, we can reach every other number through some combination of 5 under _9","Like the previous answer, we can reach every other number through some combination of 5 under _","Like the previous answer, we can reach every other number through some combination of 5 under +0","Like the previous answer, we can reach every other number  through  some combination of 5 under +9."],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":37088,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":586686,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"There are some numbers that cannot be reached when trying to use 6 as a generator.","explanation_history":["There are some odd n","There are some od","There are some o","There are some even nu","There are some e","There are some numbers that cannot be reached when trying to use 6 as a generator."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":32832,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":619521,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting nu mber. Fo r example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":15457,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":634980,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"n-1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["n-1"],"rt":24576,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":659559,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"n-x","explain":true,"explanation":"Like the  inverse  of 2 under an element under 6 is 6-2 = 4, this can be used here substituting n for 6 and x for 2.","explanation_history":["Like hwne","Like hwn","Like hw","Like h","Like the inverse of 2 under an element under 6 is 6-2 = 4, this can be used here subs","Like the inverse of 2 under an element under 6 is 6-2 = 4, this can be used here sub","Like the inverse of 2 under an element under 6 is 6-2 = 4, this can be used here su","Like the inverse of 2 under an element under 6 is 6-2 = 4, this can be used here s","Like the inverse of 2 under an element under 6 is 6-2 = 4, this can be used here substituting x for 6 and ","Like the inverse of 2 under an element under 6 is 6-2 = 4, this can be used here substituting x f","Like the inverse of 2 under an element under 6 is 6-2 = 4, this can be used here substituting x ","Like the inverse of 2 under an element under 6 is 6-2 = 4, this can be used here substituting x","Like the inverse of 2 under an element under 6 is 6-2 = 4, this can be u sed here  substituting n for 6 and x for 2."],"response_history":["n","x-n","x-","x","n-x"],"rt":82896,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":742456,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I believe that any number can be a generator as long as: if n is odd then x must be odd, or if n is even then x must be even.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I believe that any number can be a generator as long as it is the ","I believe that any number can be a generator as long as: if the ","I believe that any number can be a generator as long as: if the","I believe that any number can be a generator as long as: if th","I believe that any number can be a g enerator  as long as: if t","I believe that any number can be a generator as long as: if n is odd then x must be odd, or if n is even then x must be even."],"rt":46767,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":789225,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":7719,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":796947,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":5293,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":802242,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":12315,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":814560,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"False","explain":true,"explanation":"I am not exactly confident, but this statement seems too broad to confirm and I can't think of all o f the ex amples.","explanation_history":["I am not quite sure but ","I am not qui","I am not qu","I am not q","I am not exactly confident, but this statement seems too broad to confirm and I can't think of all of the examples."],"response_history":["False"],"rt":92831,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":907394,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":46063,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":953459,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always , someti mes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Never","explain":true,"explanation":"I cannot figure out this question.","explanation_history":["I cannot figure out this quesiton","I cannot figure out this quesito","I cannot figure out this quesit","I cannot figure out this quesi","I cannot figure out this question."],"response_history":["Never"],"rt":711021,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1664483,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Always","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":32225,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1696710,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1800,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1698514,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"26","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["26"],"rt":2874,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1701389,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":3058,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1704447,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Multi-variable Calculus","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Multivariable Calculus","Multi-variable Calculus"],"rt":20699,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1725147,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it use d or exp lained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"4 - used it but not often or recently","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4 - used it but not often or recently"],"rt":4972,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1730121,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"4 - used it but not often or recently","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4 - used it but not often or recently"],"rt":5644,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1735767,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3331,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1739100,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2220,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1741320,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":[" 1 - not  at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2070,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1743392,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Male"],"rt":2349,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1745743,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":6935,"trial_type":"q uestion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1752679,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":5154,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1757835,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"It was interesting but the last few questions were exceptionally hard.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["It was ver","It was ve","It was v","It was interesting but the last few vqu","It was interesting but the last few vq","It was interesting but the last few v","It was interesting but the last few questions were exceptionally hard."],"rt":27801,"trial_type":" question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1785638,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]